【邪恶力量第五季11集 -- 失魂山姆】
====== E U 字幕组======
【邪恶力量・百度贴吧】首发
本字幕仅供学习 请勿商业使用
翻译: 影舞儿  castiel_RO  陌上繁花锦  绿鸟  coracc  熊熊  阳光  wangsunyaoyao
校对: 影舞儿  陌上繁花锦  coracc　　   后期: 草莓粉圆  冷月
感谢所有吧友的热心支持
EU字幕组
我不能战斗  我不能走
I can't fight. I can't walk.
但是我还能做些事情
But i can do something
我们做了一个炸弹 sam
We got everything we need ,to build a bomb, sam.
-我们到底在干嘛  -猎鬼
-what are we doing? -we are hunting a gost
谁会那么做，疯子才会
who does that,crazy peopel
我们疯了
we are insane
明日我们要去猎杀首魔
Tomorrow we hunt the devil.
这是我们在世的最后一夜了
This is our last night on earth.
用这枪给我打爆lucifer的脸
Take this thing to lucifer and empty it into his face.
你知道我永远不会伤害你
You know I'd never hurt you.
你这王八蛋给我听着
You listen to me, you son of a bitch.
我会亲手杀了你
I'm gonna kill you myself.
把你的心挖出来
I'm going to rip your heart out!
那很好啊 sam
That's good, sam.
你继续燃烧你的满腔
You keep fanning that fire in your belly --
怒火吧
All that pent-up rage.
我会很需要的
I'm gonna need it.
护士们告诉我
The nurses tell me
你拒绝服药
That, uh, you're not taking your medication.
你想谈谈为什么吗?
You want to tell me why?
Susan
Susan?
药会让我很困
The pills make me sleepy,
可是我不能(睡)
But I can't...
如果我睡着了 它就会来
If I sleep, it'll come.
你是指'怪物'
You mean the monster.
我们已经谈过这件事了
Now, we have talked about this.
它杀了Annie
But it killed Annie.
Susan 你患有精神分裂症
Susan, you're schizophrenic.
你的思想很混乱
Your mind plays...Tricks on you.
神志根本不清楚
You get confused.
有时你就会有幻觉
Sometimes you see things.
我很清楚我的状况
I know what I am.
就像我能清楚的看到 我死去的孩子再在你身后一样
Like I can see my dead son standing right behind you --
我知道他并不存在
I know he's not real.
但是这怪物是真的
But the monster -- it is real.
Annie是你的室友
Annie was your roommate,
而在她身上发生的事
And what happened to her was painful --
对我们所有人的打击都很大
For all of us.
也许对你来说 想象出一个怪物
Perhaps it's easier for you to conjure umonster
比强迫自己去面对她的自杀 更简单一些
Than to face how tragic her suicide really was.
我夜里能听见它
I can hear it at night,
在墙壁中
In the walls.
求你
Please.
你得相信我
you have to believe me.
Susan
Susan...
世界上根本没有怪物
There is no such thing as monsters.
我的天哪!
Oh, my god!
救我!
Help me!
Help me!!
他们今天晚上提前开始了啊
They're starting early tonight.
快来啊!
Hurry!
慢着! 不要理她!
Wait! Don't pay attention to her!
它来了!
It's coming!
救我!
Help me!!
救我啊!!!
啊!
Aaah!
叫人! 救我!
Get help. Help me.
你们是由芝加哥的一位Babar医生引荐来的
You were referred to me by a Dr. Babar in chicago.
是的
That's right.
好像有本儿童书籍 就是关于一只
Isn't there a children's book about an elephant
叫Babar的大象的?
named Babar?
我不知道
I don't know.
我没什么大象读物
I don't have any elephant books.
你看... 我觉得...
Look, doctor, I-I think that...
那位医生对这位根本束手无策
The Doc was in over his head with this one
因为我弟弟他有点...
Cause my brother's, uh...
好的 好的 谢了
Okay, fine. Thank you.
这-这完全没有必要
That's -- that's really not necessary.
Alex 你为什么不跟我讲讲你现在的感受
Why don't you tell me how you're feeling, alex?
我很好
I'm fine.
我是说 好吧 可能有点抑郁
I mean, okay, a little depressed, I guess.
好的 你觉得你为什么会这样
All right. Any idea why?
大概是因为我开启了天启吧
Probably because I started the apocalypse.
天启
The apocalypse?
嗯 没错
Yeah, that's right.
你认为你开启了它
And you think you started it.
呃 是啊
Well, yeah.
我是说
I-I mean
我杀了一个叫Lilith的恶魔
I killed this demon -- lilith --
不小心把Lucifer从地狱里放了出来
And I accidentally freed lucifer from hell.
所以现在他在人间 而我们正在设法阻止他的计划
So, now he's topside, and we're trying to stop him.
你和谁
W-who is?
我 和他
Me. And him.
还有 呃 一个天使
And, uh, this one angel.
哦 你是指你的良知
Oh, you mean like an angel on your shoulder?
不不 他的名字叫Castiel 他爱穿风衣
No, no. His name's castiel. He wears a trench coat.
你明白我的意思了吧 医生
See what I mean, doc?
这孩子因为这件事 沮丧了好几个月了
I mean, the kid's been beating himself up about this for months.
天启根本不是他的错
The apocalypse wasn't his fault.
不是吗
It's not?
不是
No.
还有另外一个恶魔 Ruby
There was this other demon -- Ruby.
她让他对恶魔血上了瘾
She got him addicte to demon blood.
到了最后 他几乎就是在用灌的
I mean, near the end, he was practically chugging the stuff.
我弟弟并不是恶人
My brother's not evil.
我是说 他只是
He was just...
High了
High.
是吗
Yeah?
所以你能不能治愈他我们好继续回到
So, could you fix him up so we can get back
周游美国猎杀怪物的旅途中呢
To traveling around the country and hunting monsters?
Erma
Erma...
退订我的午餐
Cancel my lunch.
Fuller医生希望你们两位都可以留院
Dr. Fuller would like to eep you both under observation
观察几天
For a couple of days.
两位 我也要吗
Both? Me too?
是的 甜心 医生认为这样最好
Yes, sugar. The doctor hinks that would be best.
好地 我只是给你来个小小的体检
All right. I'm just gonna give you a little checkup.
Ratched护士(电影角色名称) 我们把话先说清楚
All right, look, nurse ratched, let's get one thing straight --
我看过'飞越疯人院'(1975电影)
I've seen "Cuckoo's nest," So don't try
所以你甭想用你的那套镇压灵魂的权威来影响我
Any of that sou l-crushing authoritarian crap on me.
嗯
Hmm?
好啊
Okeydokey.
好地 现在你可以把裤子脱了
All right, you can go ahead and take down your pants.
等下 嗯
Wait. Mm.
为 为什么啊
What? What -- what for?
你的丝克伍澡怎么样啊 (1983年电影 丝克伍事件)
How was your silkwood shower?
还行
Okay.
好啊 嗯
Yeah. Good. Yeah.
很好 嗯 水压不错
Good, um... Good water pressure.
护士有没有...
Did the nurse --
她做的非常全面
She was very thorough.
嗯 很好 很好
Yeah. Yeah good. Good. Yeah.
我不敢相信我竟然让你把我给劝进来了
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
嘿 这是我们能该做的
Hey, it's the least we could do.
Martin救爸爸的次数 我们连数也数不过来
Martin saved dad's ass more times than we can count.
他是个很厉害的猎手
He's a great hunter.
曾经是 直到阿尔布开克(城市)事件
Was. Until Albuquerque.
再说了 我觉得我们最好还是保持忙碌 仅此而已
Besides, I-I just figure it's best we keep busy. That's all.
比什么好
Better than what?
没什么
Nothing.
好 听着 嗯
Okay, look -- um...
这几周来 我一直有点担心你
Last few weeks, you've kind of been worrying me.
哦 行了吧 Sam 别说了
Oh, come on, sam. Stop.
听好 别以为我们在疯人院里
Look, just because we're in the looney bin
你就有权给我进行什么心理解剖了
Doesn't give you the right to head-shrink me.
Dean Ellen和Jo的死
Dean. Ellen and Jo dying --
没错 是个悲剧 行不行
Yeah, it was a freakin' tragedy, okay?
但我不会纠结于此的
But I'm not gonna wallow in it.
Dean 你一直都是这样
Dean, you always do this.
你不能就这么压抑着自己
You can't just keep this crap in.
我做给你看
Watch me.
哦 他在那
Oh, there he is.
Sam Dean
Sam. Dean.
哇
Wow.
哇 你们两个都这么大了
Wow, you boys got big.
你看起来不错啊
You look good.
谢 你也是啊 Martin
Thanks. You do, too, Martin.
嗯 谢谢你们的到来
Well, thanks for coming.
呵
Yeah.
在老日子里
In the old days,
这种事就算我
I could've taken care of this thing
双手反绑也是轻而易举的
With both hands tied behind my back.
但是
But
只是 现在
Well, now...
您认为我们在猎杀什么样的东西被
What do you think it is that we're hunting?
目前我还不知道
I don't know yet.
鬼魂 恶魔 怪兽...
A ghost, demon, monster.
动物 蔬菜 矿石
Animal, vegetable, mineral.
过所医院四个月里已经死了五个人
Hospital's had five deaths in the last four months.
医生们都判定是自杀
Doctors keep calling it suicides,
但他们错了
But they're wrong.
那你看到了那东西吗
So you've seen this thing?
有人看到了那东西吗
Has anyone seen this thing?
额 有几个病人看到了 只是瞥见的
Well, a couple of patients have, uh, had glimpses,
但这事情没多大进展
But that's not a lot to go on.
他们可信吗
Are they reliable?
哦 当然 为什么不可信呢
Oh, sure. Why wouldn't they be?
呃 我也不知道
Gee, I don't know.
我知道你们两个觉得我现在只是个疯老头子
I know you boys think I'm a bag of loose screws.
那 你们可就错了
Well, you wouldn't be wrong.
我是不会给你们打电话的
But I wouldn't have called you
若非这儿有状况
Unless there was something here.
我能感觉的到
I can feel it in my gut.
我们相信你
We belive you.
你有没有检查过尸体 有没有发现什么被袭的迹象
Have you checked any of the bodies, found signs of an attack?
呃 没有
Well, uh, no.
我不 呃
I don't, uh...
我不再接近死-死尸...
I don't go around dead b-bo...
死尸了
B-bodies anymore.
Alex Eddie
Alex, eddie.
噢 很高兴见到你们在交新朋友
Well, I'm glad to see you're making friends.
你和Creaser先生来加入我们的小组吧
Why don't you and mr. Creaser join ur group?
请 这边就是
Please. Right this way.
事实上 我打算把你安排在
Actually, I'm going to be putting you
下午那组
In the afternoon group.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
嗯 老实说 呃，
Well, to be frank, uh,
你与你弟弟之间的关系
The relationship that you have with your brother
相互依赖的程度 接近危险
Seems dangerously codependent.
我想分开一段时间对你们彼此都有好处
I think a little time apart will do you both good.
好的 那么 谁愿意第一个发言
All right, so, who would like to start us off?
还有其他人吗
Anyone else?
噢 噢 噢
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
好的 Ted 冷静下来
All right, ted. Calm down.
我很冷静
I am calm.
而且我很冷静的
And I'd very calmly
想谈谈正在袭击我们的那个怪物
Like to talk about the monster that's hunting us.
Ted 我们不会再重复这个话题
Ted, we're not going to have that discussion again.
这对小组的讨论毫无帮助
It's not good for group.
我同意
I agree.
你觉得这个对小组没有帮助
You know what else isn't good for group?
一个怪物正在害我们
A monster eating all our faces off!
行了 够了 谢谢你的发言
All right, fine. Thank you.
-现在 还有其他人要说话吗 -我看到了
-Now, anyone else -I saw it!
看到它杀死了Susan
When it killed susan!
-我也是 它有一双巨大的龙虾爪 -不 它没有
-I did, too. It had big lobster clws. -No, it didn't!
是的 它是一个外星人 就像在'X档案'里
Yeah, and it was an alien, like on "X-files."
别插嘴
Stop it!
别再帮倒忙了 听我说
Stop helping! Listen to me!
我们都会死
We're all dead!
够了
That's enough!
这里根本没有什么怪物
There is no monster.
Ted 你现在需要叫护理人员吗
Now, ted, do you need me to call the orderlies...
还是打算自己放规矩点
Or can you behave?
放规矩
Behave.
太好了
King me!
Eddie
Eddie?
我是Erica cartwright医生 被安排负责你的病情
I'm dr. Erica cartwright. I've been assigned your case.
你是我的心理医生
You're my shrink?
噢 我真幸运
Well, lucky me.
而你是我带有偏执狂精神分裂
And you're m paranoid schizophrenic
自恋型人格障碍
With narcissistic personality disorder
宗教狂热心理的病人
Ad religious psychosis.
我真幸运
Lucky me.
哼
Hmm.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
当然
Yes.
事实上我有些问题想问你
I've actually got some questions for you.
真凑巧 我也有些问题想问你
What a coincidence. I've got some for you, too.
好吧 那么 作为交换 Clarice
well, then, quid pro quo, Clarice.
好的 Hannibal (食人疯子) 我先问吧
Okay, hannibal. I'll go first.
你一般晚上睡多久
How many hours a night do you sleep
每过几夜 3到4个小时
Three or four every couple of nights.
你能告诉我关于最近自杀的事吗
What can you tell me about the recent suicides in here?
都是惨事
They were tragic.
但你有没有发现一些异常的事情
But you haven't noticed anything strange,
象是 呃 黑烟 硫磺
You know, like, I don't know, black smoke, sulfur?
没有 为什么这样要问 这有什么意义
No. Why? What's that supposed to mean?
恶魔迹象
Demon signs.
我猎杀恶魔 怪物 这类的东西
I hunt demons, monsters -- that kind of thng.
你一周喝多少酒
How many drinks do you have a week?
噢 有时我得睡觉 所以--
Well, I got to sleep sometime, so --
7天乘与... 是什么
What's seven days times --
得是50多次吧
It's somewhere in the mid-50s.
你有感觉到过任何 呃 任何凉气
You ever feel any, uh, any cold spots
或者是一丝寒气在医院里飘过
Or get a chill walking throug the hospital?
我不记得我有过这样的经历 不过如果我记的呢
Not that I can remember. If I had?
这意味着有鬼魂在附近
It means there's a ghost around.
好的
Okay.
你最后一次深陷长期关系是在什么时候
When was the last time you were in a long-term relationship?
什么叫 长期
Define "Long-term."
2个月以上
More than two months.
从来没有
Never.
病人们有说过他们曾见到一些诡异的东西吗
Have the patients reported seeing anything weird?
在这里 每时每刻
In here? All the time.
好的
Right.
那么...
So...
...我们来谈谈你的父亲吧
...Let's talk about your father.
Dean 嘿
Dean. Hey.
你还好吧
You okay?
我刚才被'心理强暴'了...
I just got "Threaped."
所以 不 我并不好
So, no, I am not okay.
-求你告诉我你发现了点什么  -是的
-Tell me you found something. -Yeah.
有个人说他见过这个东西 我们该去找他谈谈
A guy says he saw the creature. We should talk to him.
一个小时后在这里会合怎样
Want to meet back here in an hour?
好 速战速决
Yeah. The sooner we take care of this thing,
我们早点离开这个鬼地方
The sooner we can get gone.
这地方令我浑身起鸡皮疙瘩
This place gives me the creeps.
嗨
Hi.
我叫Wendy
I'm wendy.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
也许这个地方也不赖
Maybe this place isn't so bad after all.
伙计
Dude...
绝对不行
You cannot hit that.
噢 左右为难
Oh, so torn.
终于 护士们已经开始巡逻了
About time. Nurses are on their rounds.
我们有 大概 15 20分钟的时间 那家伙在哪
We got, like, 15, 20 minutes. Where is this guy?
306房间
Room 306.
噢 Geez
Oh! Geez!
快点 赶紧 快点
Hurry up! Come on! Hurry up!
嘿 退后 Dean
Hey, back off, Dean!
看 找到点什么
Yeah, I found something.
你发现什么了 就在这
What do you got? Right here.
嗯 搭把手
Um...Give me a hand.
好的
All right.
这个洞横穿过他的脑部
This hole goes all the way through to his brain.
怎么回事
What does that mean?
咱看看怎么回事
Let's find out.
说真的
Seriously?
你门口看着人
You might want to keep watch.
看他脑部被吸干了
Look,his brain's been sucked dry.
太好了 有人来了
That's fascinating. Somebody's coming.
你们俩在这儿干什么呢
What are you boys doing in here?
布丁
Pudding!
好啦 出来吧 你们
All right. Come on, you two.
装疯子哦
Crazy works.
是原版的Gacy啊(2003年电影)
Are those original Gacys?
是我画的
I painted those.
讲重点吧
Back on point, please.
额 不管怎么说挺 好的
Um so whatever this thing is... Good.
溜进你的脑袋 把它 吸干
...I-it silps in your brain - sucks you dry.
嗯 是死者看上去像自杀
Yeah, then it makes the deaths look like suicides.
有想法么
Any ideas?
嗯
Yeah.
坏想法
A bad one.
什么
What is it?
额 我愿意赌你一顿鸡肉晚餐 这绝对就是我们要应付的东西
Well, I bet you a chicken dinner it's what we're up against.
死灵
A wraith.
他们撬开头骨以脑浆为食
They crack open skulls and feed on brain juice.
你往这方面想过么
You ever tangle with one before?
也不想往那想
Never wanted to, neither.
怎么消灭它
So how to kill it?
银器
Silver.
你得用银器接触死灵
You so much as touch a wraith with the stuff,
他们皮肤会剥落
And the skin will crackle.
这是好消息
Now, that's the good news.
坏消息是 他们可以化为人型
The bad news is... They can pass as humans.
可以是随便是拐角哪个叫Peter,Paul,Mary的什么人
It could be any Peter, Paul, or Mary in the joint.
好啊 怎么找出死灵
Fantastic. So how do we find it?
镜子
A-a mirror.
主说死灵真身镜中现
Lore says a wraith will show its true form in a mirror.
好 那咱们就逐一排查
Okay, well, we just got to spot-check
所有病人和医院员工
Every patient and every staff member.
好的
Okay. Yeah.
但 它为什么要在精神病院
But, I mean, what's it doing in a mental hospital?
精神病院
A nuthouse --
简直就是完美的猎物聚居区
It's -- it's -- I's a perfect captive victim pool.
对啊
Sure.
谁会相信精神病人
Who -- who's gonna believe a patient
当他们说自己看到妖怪了
When they say they saw a monster?
完美猎场啊
It's the perfect hunting ground.
怎么了 医生
What's up, doc?
你告诉我
You tell me.
猎魔
Hunting.
猎死灵 实际上
A wraith, actually.
谁都有可能是
Could be anybody.
那 我也有可能喽
So... I could be a monster?
你没嫌疑
No. You're clean.
为什么
Why you?
什么
Why me what?
为什么要猎魔呢
Why do you have to hunt monsters?
为什么不让别人做呢
Why not let someone else do it?
找不着跟我一样憨的
I can't find anybody else that dumb.
是我的工作
It's my job.
别人还忙着就其他人哪
Somebody's got to save people's asses.
也包括你
Yours included.
嗯 还有配额
So, is there a quota?
你要救多少人
How many people do you have to save?
所有人
All of them.
All of them?
你觉得自己能拯救世人
You think you have to save everyone?
嗯 拯救全世界
Yep. Whole wide world of sports.
怎么做
How?
相信我 不管你说什么 怪事我见多了
Believe me -- whatever you've got, I've heard weirder.
这是世界末日啊
It's the end of the world, okay?
是该死的天启你懂么
I mean, it's the damn biblical apocalypse.
我不去阻止它 拯救大家
And if I don't stop it and save everyone,
没人可以 我们都得死
Then no one will and we all die.
那很糟哦
That's horrible.
说的是
Yeah, tell me about it.
我是说 无论是否天启
I mean, apocalypse or no apocalypse,
有没有恶魔
Monsters or no monsters,
你肩头有着让人崩溃的责任
That's a crushing weight to have on your shoulders.
感觉六十亿人的命运都取决于你
To feel like six billion lives depend on you.
上帝啊
God.
你每天清晨是在怎样的心情中醒来的
How do you get up in the morning?
问的好
That's a good question.
你好 Eddie
Hello, eddie.
医生
Doc.
好吧
All right.
我找了三个护士站才找到这些
I had to raid three nurses' stations to get these.
它们只是镀银的 但是仍旧有用
They're only silver-plated, but they should work.
哦 不不不
Oh, no, no, no.
现在不行 甜心 拜托 径直走吧
Not today, sweetheart. Come on. Keep walking.
我
I --
现在我喜欢他
I want him now.
他更强壮
He's larger.
嗯
Hmm.
我们遇见过更糟的
You've had worse.
Fuller今晚值班
Fuller is on call tonight,
所以 我们要在没人的时候除掉他
So we'll have to hit him after lights out.
我们三个
All thre us.
什么 不
What? No!
Martin 我们要通过安全系统
Martin, we got to get past the security,
通过看护人员
Past the orderlies,
然后割破那人的喉咙
And then cut the boss man's throat, okay?
我们会结束这一切
It's gonna suck start to finish,
但是我们需要后援
But we could use the backup.
不 我不行
No, I can't.
我不行
I can't.
我们知道在albuquerque发生了什么
We know what happened in albuquerque.
你们不了解全部
You don't know the half of it.
上帝啊 我曾经和你们一样
God...I used to be just like you two.
我曾经以为我是不可战胜的
I used to think I was invincible.
然后
And then...
我发现 我不是不可战胜的
Well, I found out I'm not.
Martin 你仍旧是个猎人
Martin. You are still a hunter.
不 我不是
No, I'm not!
我没用了
I'm useless!
你认为我为什么住进加利福利亚酒店
Why you think I checked myself into the hotel california?
我尽我的一切帮助你们
I'd give anything to help you boys.
我也想
I would.
但是 我不行了
But I-I can't.
对不起 我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.
他还在这栋楼里
He's still in the building.
你去西边 我去东边
You take the west wing. I'll take the east.
啊
Aah!
不不
No! No!
看他的手臂
Look at his arm!
伤口没有出现烧焦的痕迹
The cut's not burning!
不是他
It's not him!
It's not him.
你还好吗
You okay?
不
No.
不 我不好
No, I'm not okay.
我 我 我
I...i...i...
我
I am...
很好
Awesome!
他们给你吃了什么
They give you something?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
他们 他们给了我一切
They -- they gave me everything.
它
It...
叹 叹为观止
It's spectacu...cular.
你永远是一个快乐的酗酒者
You always were a happy drunk.
Dean
Dean...
那个医生不是幽灵
The doctor wasn't a wraith.
我知道
I know.
我不明白
I don't understand it.
我的意思是 我在镜子里看见了 他不是人类
I mean, I saw it in the mirror. It wasn't human.
或者 你那是幻觉
Or you're seeing things.
也许 也许 你疯了
Maybe -- m-maybe - maybe you're going crazy.
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
好吧 来
Well, come on.
我的意思是 你至少 在很长一段时间里 是不太正常的
I mean, you've been at least... Half crazy for a long time.
从你从地狱回来之后
Since you got back from hell --
或者 甚至在那之前
Or since before that, even.
而且我们在 我们在一个精神病院
And we're in a - we're in a mental hospital.
或许 或许你最终精神分裂了
Ma-maybe -- maybe you finally cracked.
你知道 也许
You know, maybe --
也许 现在 你真的 真的疯了
Maybe now you are really, for-real crazy.
我知道是我的错
I made a mistake  That's all
不过 我会把他找出来的
I'll find the thing
好的 我知道你会的
Okay Yeah yeah yeah yeah I know I know.
没关系的
It's okay  Hey
嗨 看着我
Hey   look at me
这些都不重要
It's okay...
因为你是我哥哥
Cause you're my broter...
我依然爱着你
And I still love ya
额
Mm
啵
Boop
今天的治疗你怎么没来
You missed our session today
我没时间
I'm a little busy
你还在找那个鬼魂啊
Still hunting that wraith
我不能看着人们一个个死去
People are dying
这是自然规律 每时每刻都有人死去啊
People die all the time
听着 我的女士 请你
Look lady why don't you
不要打扰我的工作  这也许是在救你的命
just let me do my job  maybe save your life
我并不担心我的生命 我担心的是你
It's not my life that I'm worried about
天哪 别说了 我很好 不需要你担心
Oh my go I am fine okay
真的 我很好
I'm fine
别骗自己了 连你自己都不相信那写鬼魂的事情 对吧
Come on  Even you don't believe that
你给自己的压力太大了
All this pressure that you're putting yourself under
这些负罪感会让你窒息的
All this guilt,it's killing you
你不可能拯救所有人
You can't save everybody
你不能
You can't
该死的 Dean 这些天你救过谁
Hell  these days  you can't save anybody Dean
你说什么 Dean 不要逃避 我说的是事实
What'd you say  The truth  dean
你让Ellen和Jo都死掉了
You got Ellen and Jo killed
你对着Lucifer开枪  可你却杀不了他
You shot Lucifer,but you couldn't gank him
你甚至阻止不了sam杀死lilith
You couldn't stop sam from killing lilith
对了 是你打破的第一个封印
And oh yeah you broke the first seal
你做的一切都失败了
All you do is fail
Dean 你真的认为就凭你一个人
Did you really think that you Dean Winchester
拿了个本科毕业证  加上你那些让他们下地狱的妄想
With a G.E.D. And a give-'em-hell attitude
就能够杀死那些恶魔
Were gonna beat the devil
你太天真了
Please
这个世界就要毁灭了
The world is gonna burn
你只能坐以待毙
And there is nothing that you can do about it
你是谁
Who are you
你怎么知道这些
How do you know that stuff
嗨 伙计 别闹了
Hey  Settle down
告诉我
Tell me
我说了 别闹了
I said settle down
你是
Are you...
她是谁
Who is she
谁
Who
你瞎了啊 她就站在这啊
What are you blind,her
伙计 那根本没人啊
Pal,there's nobody there
Dean 我不是真实存在的
I'm not real,Dean
我潜伏在你的脑子里
I'm in your head...
因为你快疯掉了
Cause you are going crazy
让我一个人呆会
Just leave me alone
你要见我么
You asked to see me
是的 谢谢你能来
Yeah.Thanks
额 我
I  um...
我只是想向您道歉
I just wanted to apologize
我对我多做的一切感到十分的抱歉
I feel horrible about what I did to you
我还以为你是个恶魔
I thought you were a monster
我知道
I know that
但是 我想不通的是为什么
The question is,why
我
I I was..
这些都无所谓 嗯
It doesn't matter  um...
因为经历了昨晚的一切
Because after what happened last night
我有
I,I had a...
一刻让我感到了身边的人的宽厚
Moment of clarity
额
Um...
我知道这里根本没有恶魔
I realized there's no such thing as monsters
我很高兴你能这么说
Well,I'm...Glad to hear you say that
但是 老实说
But honestly
至少恶魔的问题还是你的精神上的问题
Monsters are the least of your problems
人们可以学会在幻觉中生活
People can learn to live with delusions
但是 我在你眼中看到了愤怒
But the anger I saw in you
我
I...
你伤害了那两个人 你差点杀了他们
You hurt those two men and you were going to kill me
当你追赶我时 你的眼神
The look in your eyes when you came after me
我
I...
就好像你几乎不是个有自控能力人
It was like you were barely even human
像一个被附身的人
Like a man possessed
我知道
I know
对不起
Please...
只是
Just...
你能再给我一次机会吗
Could you give me a second chance
恩 这里不是监狱
Well,this isn't a prison
我允许你呆在休息室里
You'll be allowed to go to the day room
不过 要被监管
Under supervision
好的 谢谢
Thank you
不过 如果你的精神病再一次发作
But if there is one more outburst
我会把你绑在一台机器上
I wll transfer you to a facility
一台专门解决有暴力问题病人的机器
That's equipped to handle violent patients
相信我 他们可没有我这么仁慈
And believe me they will be far far less forgiving
嗨 Dean
Dean. Hey.
呃 怎么了
Whoa. What's wrong?
那跟恶魔血没有关系 sam
It's not the demon blood, sam.
从来都没有
It never was.
什么?
What?
有问题的是你
The problem was you.
一直都是你
It was always you --
那些谎言 你的傲慢
The lies, your arrogance,
还有你灵魂上的黑点
That black spot on your soul.
因为你 现在我们都得死
Now we're all gonna die because of you.
那全是你的错 是你害了我们
It's all your fault! You killed all of us!
可悲的怪物
Pathetic freak!
你这个XXX的恶魔
You evil son of a bitch!
笨蛋
Loser!
我们全都会死 怪物
We're all gonna die! Freak!
笨蛋
Loser!
怪物
Freak!
啊
Aah!
别来烦我
Leave me alone!
Leave me alone!!
别来烦我
Leave me alone! No!
快停下 别来烦我
Stop it! Leave me alone!
离我远一点 我什么都没做
Leave me alone! I didn't do it!
我说离我远一点 这根本不关我的事
Get off of me! Leave me alone!
噢 不
Aah! No!
离我远一点
Leave me alone!
怎么了
What's happening?
发生了什么
Martin Martin 是我 我是Dean
Martin, martin, it's me! It's dean!
哦 对不起
Oh. Sorry.
你看上去很不好
You -- you look like hell, boy.
我感觉很不好
I feel -- I feel like it, too.
Sam在哪里
Where's sam?
被锁起来了
Lockdown.
感谢上帝 他疯了
He went crazy, thank god.
什么?
What?
我也快疯了
I'm going crazy, too.
我现在有幻觉 还会幻听
I'm seeing things. I'm hearing things.
我们两个都是
W-we both are.
『疯』就是线索
Crazy's the clue.
你是什么意思
W-what do you mean?
-Dean -『疯』就是线索
-Dean? -Crazy's the clue.
是 你说过了 究竟怎么?
Y-you said that. What?
我的意思是 我和Sam做过的那些事
I mean, the things that me and sam have done,
那些... 我们见过的东西
The -- the stuff we've seen --
我们早晚有一天都会秀逗的
We're gonna end up going guano eventually,
很可能最后我们都会变成两个流着口水的老疯子
Probably end up like a couple of drooling nutbags.
没有冒犯的意思
No offense.
没事
None taken.
但是我和他在同一天 一起疯了
But me and him freaking out on the same day?
我的意思是 那绝对...
I mean, it -- it -- it's got to be the...
-怪物 -在哪里 在哪里
-The monster. -What?! Where? Where?
不 不 那里什么都没有
No, not -- no, there's nothing there.
你看
Look...
如果这个怪物不是以疯子为食的话怎么办?
...What if this thing doesn't feed on the insane?
也许就是它让人们疯发疯
What if it makes people insane?
这可能吗? 这看起来像真的吗?
Is that possible? Does -- does that seem real?
呃 我... 我不是很可靠的
Well, I-I'm -- I'm not the most reliable source
在什么是'真实的'这一点上
On what is "Real,"
但那听起来 有道理
But it sounds -- makes sense.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 所以假设我们被感染了
Okay, so -- s-so we got infected.
呃 什么东西让我们疯狂了
You know, something shot us up with crazy.
你知道的 一些...
You know, something...
或许...
Maybe...
也许是我父亲的鬼魂
Maybe it was the ghost of my dad.
不
No.
重点是亡灵 Dean
Focus on the wraith, dean.
这是重点 对 亡灵 那个亡灵
Focus! Right, the wraith. The wraith.
好吧 所以那只亡灵
Okay, so the wraith -- the wraith.
它 它对我们下了毒
It -- it poisoned us.
它...
It...
也许是有毒的 你知道 通过触摸
Maybe with venom, you know, by t-- by touch.
或者是有毒的液体 比如... 唾液
Or -- or -- or venom or, um, saliva.
Wendy
Wendy.
Wendy?
就是她 我和Sam身上到处都是她的口水
Wendy! Wendy slobbered all over me and sam!
我们就是这样被感染的
That's how we got infected!
我不能踩裂缝
I can't step on the cracks.
这是真的吗?
Is this real?
哦 是的 甜心
Oh, it is, sugar.
真的不能再真了
It's very real.
啊
Aaah!
她还活着
She's still alive!
Wendy的房间里有两个病人
There's two patients in Wendy's room.
他们袭击了我
They attacked me.
Dean  你听得到我说话吗?
Dean? Can you hear me?
Dean!
你必须离开这里 并且杀了那个东西
You've got to get out there and kill that thing.
我会照顾她的
I'll take care of her.
我 我不行
I-I can't.
你必须得去 孩子 你现在没有选择
You have to. You have no choice, son.
走
go!
Dean 快走
Dean, run!
走啊
Run!
嘿 放开我
Hey! Let me go!
不行
No.
你太愤怒了 绝对不能放你回到现实世界
You are far too angry to be out there in the real world.
-是你! -当然是我
-You! -Of course it's me.
我说真的 你们猎手 真的是闻名不如见面啊
I got to say, you hunters don't exactly live up to your rep.
我说 Martin根本一无是处 一点威胁也没有
I mean, martin's a wreck. He's harmless.
然后你和你哥来到这里
And you and your brother come in here,
叫嚷着要杀怪物
Talking tough about killing monsters?
真的很惹人注意
Kind of made you easy to spot.
然后我只需轻轻一碰...
Then all it took was a touch...
你就是我的了
...And you were mine.
...哦 我太喜欢这里了
Oh, I love it in here.
这地方可是我的私人五星级餐馆
This place is my own personal five-star restaurant.
嗯
Mmm.
疯子们的大脑 里面被灌满了多巴胺和肾上腺素
Crazy brains -- they get soaked in dopamine and adrenaline
还有各种各样的激素和化学物质
And just all sorts of hormones and chemicals
真的是 太可口了
That make them delicious.
而且 他们越疯癫 吃起来就越美味
And crazier they are, the better they taste.
这一切都是你干的
You did this to me!
呃 我只是帮了点忙而已
Well...I helped.
但是那些怒火
But that rage?
不不不 那可都是你
No, no, no, no. That's all you.
我不能把人变疯 我只是刺激一下那些已经存在的情感而已
I don't make crazy. I just crank up what's already there.
是你们自己画地为牢的
You build your own hell.
我只是提供砖块而已
But I give you the legos.
而当你们成熟了以后...
And when you're ripe...
我就会让你们的忧虑 全部消失
...I make all of your problems dsappear.
你给我离他远点
You get away from him!
你以为你这样真的会有好的结果吗 小子
Do you really think this is gonna end well for you, kiddo?
不
No.
不过反正我已经疯了 豁出去算了
But I'm crazy, so what the hell.
啊!
Aaaah!
你还是疯子吗?
You still crazy?
也就和平常一样疯吧
Not any more than usual.
-我们得赶快离开 -是啊
-We got to get out of here. -Yeah.
看起来Tom Cruise没错啊 医生们都是混蛋
Well, looks like Tom cruise was right. Shrinks suck.
你怎么了
What are you doing?
Sammy 你没事吧
Sammy you okay?
我有事
No.
-不 那只亡灵 -怎么
-No, the wraith -what about her?
她说的对
She was right.
不 她说的很错 她已经死了 好不好
No, she wasn't. She's dead, okay?
我们上路吧 我得来瓶酒 也许12瓶...
Let's hit the road. I need a drink. Or 12.
平时我能把这情绪隐藏起来
Most of the time I can hide it,
但是 我真的很生气
But...I am angry.
我几乎对什么都看不顺眼
I'm mad at everything.
以前我是气你和老爸
I used to be mad at you and dad,
之后是Lilith 而现在是Lucifer
Then Lilith, now it's lucifer.
而 而且我还给自己找理由 我怪Ruby或是恶魔血
A-and I make excuses. I blame ruby or the demon blood.
但这不是他们的错 错的人其实是我
But it's not their fault. It's not them. It's me.
都是我心底的那些...
It's inside me.
我根本每一刻都在发怒...
I am mad all the time...
而连我都不知道为什么
And I don't know why.
够了 别说了
Okay, stop.
别再说了
Stop it.
就算你是又怎样
So what if you are?
你想怎么办 请个假
What are you gonna do, take a leave of absence?
你打算对Lucifer臣服
You gonna say yes to lucifer?
什么
What?
不 我当然不会 我-
No, of course not. I --
没错
Exactly.
而你就是要这样做
And that's exactly what you're gonna do.
你必须把你的那些乱七八糟的情绪整理好
You're gonna take all that crap,
然后深深的埋到心底
And you're gonna bury it.
然后遗忘
You're gonna forget about it...
因为只有这样我们才能继续
Because that's how we keep going.
只有这样我们才不会有一天变得和Martin一样!
That's how we don't end up like Martin!
你跟我吗?
Are you with me?
说话 你究竟跟不跟我?
Come on, man. Are you with me?
我跟你
I'm with you.
那就好
Good.
我们走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.